<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollingText</string>
    <string name="article_title">CHRISTIAN MATURITY</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Understanding Maturity</string>
    <string name="article_text">•	First let’s look at the concept of birth and growth. When a child is born, it is expected that he should grow. Parents become agitated and tensed up when there is no physical evidence of Growth in a child. In fact most physical deformities are associated with the concept of abnormal growth or the complete absence of growth. \n
\n •	A second concept will be the idea of going upstream where there is a slope you have to climb. When climbing it could seem tasking and overwhelming and demoralizing. It usually requires a lot of effort. At some point the temptation to stop halfway is always there. But the more you stop, the more difficult it is to continue climbing up. But when you make a habit of going upstream from time to time, it becomes easier and less daunting. \n
        \n <b> Growth is similar in concept</b> with these two instances but far more important. \n
\n Growth is a development or improvement towards a goal. In the case of a child, it is a growth towards adulthood and for someone going upstream, it is the desire to reach the end point.\n
\n When one is born again, he is like a new born baby or someone at the beginning of an important journey. Such a person is spiritually immature. As time passes, it is expected that he should develop the character or qualities that the Bible says marks a mature Christian. \n
\nIn Ephesians 4:14-15 we are expected to no longer be children but grow up in Christ. Peter speaking in 2Peter 3:18 encouraged us to grow in the grace and knowledge of our Lord Jesus Christ and in 2 Thess 1:3  Paul mentions that Thessalonians grew exceedingly in faith.\n\n
        \n <i> For more information, search for Christian Maturity in www.google.com</i>
</string>
    <string name="add_comment">Add Comment</string>
</resources>